[
    {
        "lessonName": "Introduction",
        "lessonID": 1,
        "hints": 3,
        "exercises": [
            {
                "type": "explanation",
                "question": "The Alphabet",
                "explanation": "Before starting to learn Lithuanian, you should know that the Lithuanian uses the latin alphabet, however it has a few additional letters.<br>-'ą' is a long and 'a' is a short sound (l<b>u</b>ck - short, <b>a</b>rchitecture - long)<br>Same goes for: <br>-'ę' and 'e' (<b>e</b>nvelope - short, el<b>a</b>stic - long)<br>-'į' and 'i' (<b>i</b>mp - short, <b>ea</b>ting - long)<br>-'ų' and 'u' (y<b>ou</b> - long, p<b>u</b>t - short)<br>And then there are: <br>'č' (<b>ch</b>ips), 'ž' (plea<b>ss</b>ure), 'š' (<b>sh</b>ampoo),  'ė' (nightm<b>are</b>), 'y' (mach<b>i</b>ne), 'ū' (m<b>oo</b>n)<br>"
            },
            {
                "type": "explanation",
                "question": "Let's say hi in Lithuanian",
                "explanation": "Hi/Hello - Labas<br>Polite/Plural - Sveiki<br>Female/Male - Sveika/Sveikas<br><br>Labas rytas - Good morning<br>Laba diena - Good day<br>Labas vakaras - Good evening"
            },
            {
                "type": "multiChoice",
                "question": "Hello - ",
                "correctAnswer": "Labas",
                "extraAnswers": [
                    "Labu",
                    "Labai"
                ],
                "shuffleAnswers": true
            },
            {
                "type": "multiSelect",
                "question": "Hello (Select all that apply) ",
                "correctAnswers": [
                    "Sveiki",
                    "Labas",
                    "Sveikas"
                ],
                "shuffleAnswers": true,
                "extraAnswers": [
                    "Labai",
                    "Sala"
                ]
            },
            {
                "type": "explanation",
                "question": "Gender",
                "explanation": "You might have noticed that there are multiple ways to use Sveiki. <br>That is because you can use it differently, depending on what gender the person you're speaking to is. <br>Every noun has either a male or female gender and every gender has many word endings, but the most common are:<br>'a','ė' for female (mam<b>a</b>-mum) and <br>'as', 'is' for male (stal<b>as</b>-table)"
            },
            {
                "type": "explanation",
                "question": "Plural",
                "explanation": "Every noun, verb or adjective, in Lithuanian, has a different ending depending on it's plurality. <br>For example, 2 small tables would translate to <br>2 maži stalai, whereas one small table is <br>1 mažas stalas<br> (Notice the different endings)<br>Plural is also used to approach someone you don't know or someone you respect, <br>e.g. Sveiki, broli (Hello, brother)<br>Some words can be male or female, e.g. <i>stundetas/studentė</i> student(male/female)"
            },
            {
                "type": "inputText",
                "question": "Write: 'Hello, mum'",
                "answers": [
                    "Labas, mama",
                    "Sveika, mama",
                    "Sveiki, mama"
                ]
            },
            {
                "type": "multiSelect",
                "question": "Select all: 'Hello, mum' ",
                "correctAnswers": [
                    "Sveika, mama",
                    "Sveiki, mama"
                ],
                "shuffleAnswers": true,
                "extraAnswers": [
                    "Sveikas, mama",
                    "Labas, stalas",
                    "Sveika, mum"
                ]
            },
            {
                "type": "multiSelect",
                "question": "Select all words that are of female gender",
                "correctAnswers": [
                    "mama",
                    "gėlė"
                ],
                "shuffleAnswers": true,
                "extraAnswers": [
                    "tėtis",
                    "stalas"
                ]
            },
            {
                "type": "explanation",
                "question": "Articles",
                "explanation": "There are no articles in Lithuanian. All words are equally important, so 'gėlė' means 'the flower' and 'a flower' "
            },
            {
                "type": "multiSelect",
                "question": "Select all words that are of male gender",
                "correctAnswers": [
                    "rokas"
                ],
                "shuffleAnswers": true,
                "extraAnswers": [
                    "mama",
                    "kėdė"
                ]
            },
            {
                "type": "multiChoice",
                "question": "Which one is <b>incorrect</b> ?",
                "correctAnswer": "Sveika, tėtis",
                "extraAnswers": [
                    "Labas, mama",
                    "Sveiki, mama"
                ],
                "shuffleAnswers": true
            },
            {
                "type": "explanation",
                "question": "Introduce Yourself",
                "explanation": " <i>Labas, mano vardas yra</i><br>Hello, my name is<br><br><i>Aš esu<i/><br>I am<br><br><i>Koks yra tavo vardas?</i><br>What is your name?"
            },
            {
                "type": "multiChoice",
                "question": "Name - ?",
                "correctAnswer": "vardas",
                "extraAnswers": [
                    "labas",
                    "tavo"
                ],
                "shuffleAnswers": true
            },
            {
                "type": "inputText",
                "question": "Write: 'name'",
                "answers": [
                    "vardas"
                ]
            },
            {
                "type": "multiChoice",
                "question": "my, yours - ?",
                "correctAnswer": "mano, tavo",
                "extraAnswers": [
                    "tavo, mano",
                    "mano, savo"
                ],
                "shuffleAnswers": true
            },
            {
                "type": "explanation",
                "question": "Verb Assumption",
                "explanation": "Sometimes, you can assume that a word is in the sentence, even if it's not written so.<br>Most commonly it is assumed that the word 'is' is in the sentence.<br>E.g. <i>Mano vardas - Simona</i><br> My name (is) Simona<br>Note that the assumed word is replaced with a dash."
            },
            {
                "type": "inputText",
                "question": "Write: 'My name is Simona'",
                "answers": [
                    "Mano vardas yra Simona",
                    "Mano vardas - Simona"
                ]
            },
            {
                "type": "inputText",
                "question": "Write: 'I am Simona'",
                "answers": [
                    "Aš esu  Simona",
                    "Aš - Simona"
                ]
            },
            {
                "type": "multiChoice",
                "question": "Which one is <b>incorrect</b>?",
                "correctAnswer": "Tu esu Aleksas",
                "extraAnswers": [
                    "Aš - Aleksas",
                    "Mano vardas - Aleksas"
                ],
                "shuffleAnswers": true
            },
            {
                "type": "multiSelect",
                "question": "Select all words that are of male gender",
                "correctAnswers": [
                    "Aleksas",
                    "kompiuteris"
                ],
                "shuffleAnswers": true,
                "extraAnswers": [
                    "kėdė"
                ]
            },
            {
                "type": "multiSelect",
                "question": "Select all 'I am'",
                "correctAnswers": [
                    "Aš esu",
                    "Aš -"
                ],
                "shuffleAnswers": true,
                "extraAnswers": [
                    "Aš - Aleksas"
                ]
            },
            {
                "type": "explanation",
                "question": "Say Goodbye",
                "explanation": "Just like saying hello, saying goodbye can be translated into many words<br><i>Viso gero/Sudie</i> - Goodbye<br><i>Ate</i> - Bye<br><i>Iki pasimatymo or Iki</i> - See you later or See you"
            },
            {
                "type": "inputText",
                "question": "Write: 'Goodbye'",
                "answers": [
                    "Ate",
                    "Sudie",
                    "Viso gero"
                ]
            },
            {
                "type": "inputText",
                "question": "Write: 'See you later'",
                "answers": [
                    "Iki",
                    "Iki pasimatymo"
                ]
            },
            {
                "type": "multiSelect",
                "question": "Select all that express the phrase 'goodbye'",
                "correctAnswers": [
                    "Sudie",
                    "Viso Gero"
                ],
                "shuffleAnswers": true,
                "extraAnswers": [
                    "Iki"
                ]
            },
            {
                "type": "multiSelect",
                "question": "Select all that express the word 'see you'",
                "correctAnswers": [
                    "Iki",
                    "Iki pasimatymo"
                ],
                "shuffleAnswers": true,
                "extraAnswers": [
                    "Sudie"
                ]
            },
            {
                "type": "explanation",
                "question": "Personal Pronouns",
                "explanation": "There are 8 personal pronouns in Lithuanian: <br>Aš - I<br Tu - You<br> Jis - He<br> Ji - She<br><br> Mes - We<br>Jūs - You<br> Jie - They<br>Jos - They (group of only females)"
            },
            {
                "type": "multiChoice",
                "question": "Translate: 'Ji yra Simona'",
                "correctAnswer": "She is Simona",
                "extraAnswers": [
                    "They are called Simona",
                    "He is Simona"
                ],
                "shuffleAnswers": true
            },
            {
                "type": "multiChoice",
                "question": "Which one is <b>incorrect</b>?",
                "correctAnswer": "Jis - Simona",
                "extraAnswers": [
                    "Ji - Simona",
                    "Jis - Ignas",
                    "Jis yra Ignas"
                ],
                "shuffleAnswers": true
            },
            {
                "type": "multiSelect",
                "question": "Select all that are depicting only the female gender",
                "correctAnswers": [
                    "Ji yra Simona"
                ],
                "shuffleAnswers": true,
                "extraAnswers": [
                    "Jis yra Ignas",
                    "Jie yra Ignai"
                ]
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "lessonName": "Declension",
        "lessonID": 2,
        "hints": 5,
        "exercises": [
            {
                "type": "explanation",
                "question": "What are cases?",
                "explanation": "In Lithuanian every noun, adjective and adverb has a different ending depending on the position and intent of the word.<br><br>A cat is in the <b>house</b> <i>vs</i> A cat is on the <b>house</b><br>The word '<b>house</b>' stays the same.<br><br>Katė/Katinas yra <b>name</b> <i>vs</i> Katė/Katinas yra ant <b>namo</b><br> In this case, the word '<b>namas</b>' has a different ending, depending on its position relative to the cat. <br> Some cases are usually used with specific prepositions."
            },
            {
                "type": "explanation",
                "question": "Types of Cases",
                "explanation": "There are 7 cases in the modern Lithuanian language and in simple terms, almost every case answers a question.<br><br><i>Vardininkas</i> (Nominative) - Kas? (What/Who is?)<br><i>Kilmininkas</i> (Genitive) - Ko? (Of what/Whose?)<br><i>Naudininkas</i> (Dative) - Kam? (What for? For what purpose?)<br><i>Galininkas</i> (Accusative) - Ką? (What object is interacted with? What time?)<br><i>Įnagininkas</i> (Instrumentative) - Kuo? (With what?)<br><i>Kilmininkas</i> (Locative) - Kur? (Where?)<br><i>Šauksmininkas</i> (Exclamatory) - (used to address somebody)"
            },
            {
                "type": "explanation",
                "question": "Nominative - Vardininkas",
                "explanation": "The Nominative case describes the basic state of the object. It also usually defines which specific word endings you will use in other cases.<br><br> e.g. <b>Telefonas</b> yra name. (A <b>telephone</b> is in the house.)<br><b>Katė</b> bėga. (A <b>cat</b> is running.)<br><br>In both cases the telephone and the cat are the main subjects. <br><i>They</i> are interacting with the world."
            },
            {
                "type": "multiChoice",
                "question": "Which word has the Nominative case: <br>Mama yra ant namo <br>(Mum is on the house)",
                "correctAnswer": "Mama",
                "extraAnswers": [
                    "yra",
                    "namo"
                ],
                "shuffleAnswers": true
            },
            {
                "type": "multiChoice",
                "question": "Which word has the Nominative case: <br>Saulė kyla. <br>(The sun rises)",
                "correctAnswer": "Saulė",
                "extraAnswers": [
                    "kyla"
                ],
                "shuffleAnswers": true
            },
            {
                "type": "multiSelect",
                "question": "Select all words that have the Nominative case: <br>Aš ir Tomas esame draugai. <br>(I and Tomas are friends.)",
                "correctAnswers": [
                    "Aš",
                    "Tomas"
                ],
                "shuffleAnswers": true,
                "extraAnswers": [
                    "esame"
                ]
            },
            {
                "type": "multiChoice",
                "question": "Which question does the Nominative case answer?",
                "correctAnswer": "kas? (what?)",
                "extraAnswers": [
                    "kur? (where?)",
                    "kada? (when?)"
                ],
                "shuffleAnswers": true
            },
            {
                "type": "explanation",
                "question": "Genitive - Kilmininkas",
                "explanation": "The Genitive case can describe the object's possessive status and state (with certain verbs). It is also used when describing a part of an object.<br>e.g. <b>Mano</b> mama yra Aldona. (<b>My</b> mum is Aldona.) - Possession.<br>Aš mačiau dalį <b>filmo</b>. (I saw a part <b>of the film.</b>) - Part of an object. <br><br> The most common endings for Genitive is 'o' (stal<b>o</b>) and 'ės'(kėd<b>ės</b>), sometimes making the word identical to its plural form. <br> With some prepositions Genitive words are used to define location."
            },
            {
                "type": "multiChoice",
                "question": "Which word is in the Genitive case: <br>Deividas turi savo namą.<br>(David has his own house.)",
                "correctAnswer": "savo",
                "extraAnswers": [
                    "Deividas",
                    "turi",
                    "namą"
                ],
                "shuffleAnswers": true
            },
            {
                "type": "multiChoice",
                "question": "Which word is in the Genitive case: <br>Telefono laidas yra senas. <br>(The telephone's wire is old.)",
                "correctAnswer": "Telefono",
                "extraAnswers": [
                    "laidas",
                    "senas"
                ],
                "shuffleAnswers": false
            },
            {
                "type": "multiChoice",
                "question": "Which word is in the Genitive case: <br>Ten yra pusė obuolio. <br>(There is half an apple.) ",
                "correctAnswer": "obuolio",
                "extraAnswers": [
                    "Ten",
                    "pusė"
                ],
                "shuffleAnswers": false
            },
            {
                "type": "multiSelect",
                "question": "The Genitive case is <b>not</b> used to...",
                "correctAnswers": [
                    "Explain purpose",
                    "Address someone"
                ],
                "shuffleAnswers": true,
                "extraAnswers": [
                    "Express state of object",
                    "Express possession"
                ]
            },
            {
                "type": "inputText",
                "question": "Write: My cat's",
                "answers": [
                    "Mano katės",
                    "Mano katino"
                ]
            },
            {
                "type": "multiChoice",
                "question": "Which word is in the Genitive case: <br>Simonos veidas<br>(Simone's face)",
                "correctAnswer": "Simonos",
                "extraAnswers": [
                    "veidas"
                ],
                "shuffleAnswers": true
            },
            {
                "type": "explanation",
                "question": "Dative - Naudininkas",
                "explanation": "The Dative case describes the purpose or the addressee. <br>e.g. Aš perku maistą <b>katinui</b>. (I buy food <b>for the cat</b>.)<br><b>Obuoliai</b> mamai. (Apples <b>for mum</b>.) <br> The most common endings are 'ui' (katin<b>ui</b>), 'ei' (kat<b>ei</b>), 'ai'(mam<b>ai</b>) "
            },
            {
                "type": "multiChoice",
                "question": "Which word is in the Dative case?",
                "correctAnswer": "mamai",
                "extraAnswers": [
                    "mama",
                    "mamos"
                ],
                "shuffleAnswers": true
            },
            {
                "type": "multiChoice",
                "question": "Which word is in the Dative case?",
                "correctAnswer": "katei",
                "extraAnswers": [
                    "katės",
                    "katė"
                ],
                "shuffleAnswers": true
            },
            {
                "type": "multiChoice",
                "question": "Which word is in the Dative case?",
                "correctAnswer": "namui",
                "extraAnswers": [
                    "telefonas",
                    "mamos"
                ],
                "shuffleAnswers": true
            },
            {
                "type": "multiChoice",
                "question": "Which word is in the Dative case:<br> Man 15 metų. <br>(I am 15 years old.)",
                "correctAnswer": "Man",
                "extraAnswers": [
                    "metų"
                ],
                "shuffleAnswers": true
            },
            {
                "type": "multiChoice",
                "question": "Which word is in the Dative case?",
                "correctAnswer": "kompiuteriui",
                "extraAnswers": [
                    "kompiuteris",
                    "kompiuterio"
                ],
                "shuffleAnswers": true
            },
            {
                "type": "multiSelect",
                "question": "Which phrases do <b>not</b> contain any words in the Dative case?",
                "correctAnswers": [
                    "Mamos katinas",
                    "Mano katė"
                ],
                "shuffleAnswers": true,
                "extraAnswers": [
                    "Mano katei",
                    "Tavo katinui"
                ]
            },
            {
                "type": "explanation",
                "question": "Accusative - Galininkas",
                "explanation": "The Accusative case describes an object, which is being interacted with. It is also used when describing future and past time. Most singular Accusative words end in 'ą', 'ę', į'.<br>e.g. Perku <b>maistą</b> katinui. (I buy <b>food</b> for the cat.)<br>Duodu <b>obuolį</b> mamai. (I give <b>an apple</b> to mum.) <br>Aš dirbsiu <b>pirmadienį</b>. (I will work <b>on Monday</b>.)<br>"
            },
            {
                "type": "multiChoice",
                "question": "Which word is in Accusative case:<br> Aš skaitau laikraštį. <br>(I read a newspaper.)",
                "correctAnswer": "laikraštį",
                "extraAnswers": [
                    "Aš",
                    "skaitau"
                ],
                "shuffleAnswers": true
            },
            {
                "type": "multiChoice",
                "question": "Which word is in Accusative case:<br> Aš matau saulę. <br>(I see the sun.)",
                "correctAnswer": "saulę",
                "extraAnswers": [
                    "Aš",
                    "matau"
                ],
                "shuffleAnswers": true
            },
            {
                "type": "multiChoice",
                "question": "Which word is in Accusative case:<br> Mama žiūri filmą. <br>(Mum is watching a film.)",
                "correctAnswer": "filmą",
                "extraAnswers": [
                    "Mama",
                    "žiūri"
                ],
                "shuffleAnswers": true
            },
            {
                "type": "inputText",
                "question": "Write in Accusative case: 'mum'",
                "answers": [
                    "mamą"
                ]
            },
            {
                "type": "multiChoice",
                "question": "Which word is the right form of Accusative for the word 'katė'?",
                "correctAnswer": "katę",
                "extraAnswers": [
                    "katino",
                    "katės"
                ],
                "shuffleAnswers": true
            },
            {
                "type": "multiSelect",
                "question": "Which word is <b>not</b> in accusative form?",
                "correctAnswers": [
                    "filmo"
                ],
                "extraAnswers": [
                    "filmą",
                    "katę",
                    "tetį"
                ],
                "shuffleAnswers": true
            },
            {
                "type": "multiSelect",
                "question": "The Accusative case is used to...",
                "correctAnswers": [
                    "express interactivity",
                    "express time in the past and the future"
                ],
                "shuffleAnswers": true,
                "extraAnswers": [
                    "express time in the present",
                    "express possession"
                ]
            },
            {
                "type": "multiChoice",
                "question": "Which word is in the Accusative case:<br>Pirmadienį, katė valgo. <br>(On Monday, the cat eats.)",
                "correctAnswer": "Pirmadienį",
                "extraAnswers": [
                    "valgo",
                    "katė"
                ],
                "shuffleAnswers": true
            },
            {
                "type": "explanation",
                "question": "Instrumentative - Įnagininkas",
                "explanation": "The Instrumentative case describes the object that the verb is being done <i>with</i>. <br>If Accusative is 'I'm carrying an <b>apple</b>', then Instrumentative is 'I'm carrying an apple <b>with my hands</b>'. <br>e.g. Aš važiuoju<b> automobiliu</b>. (I'm driving <b>with an automobile</b>.)<br>Aš mojuoju <b>ranka</b>. (I'm waving <b>with a hand</b>.) <br>Tėtis rašo <b>pieštuku</b>. (Dad is writing <b>with a pencil</b>.)<br>"
            },
            {
                "type": "multiChoice",
                "question": "Which word is in the Instrumentative case:<br>Katė valgo su šakute. <br>(The cat eats with a fork.)",
                "correctAnswer": "šakute",
                "extraAnswers": [
                    "valgo",
                    "katė",
                    "su"
                ],
                "shuffleAnswers": true
            },
            {
                "type": "multiChoice",
                "question": "Which word is in the Instrumentative case:<br>Katinas valgo su kate. <br>(The cat eats with (another) cat.)",
                "correctAnswer": "kate",
                "extraAnswers": [
                    "katinas",
                    "valgo"
                ],
                "shuffleAnswers": true
            },
            {
                "type": "multiChoice",
                "question": "What question does the Instrumentative answer?",
                "correctAnswer": "(su) kuo? - (with) what?",
                "extraAnswers": [
                    "ką? - what?",
                    "kodėl? - why?"
                ],
                "shuffleAnswers": true
            },
            {
                "type": "explanation",
                "question": "Locative - Vietininkas",
                "explanation": "The Locative case describes location. <br><br>e.g. Aš esu <b>parduotuvėje</b>. (I am <b>in a shop</b>.)<br>Aš gyvenu <b>mieste</b>. (I live <b>in a city</b>.)<br><br> The most common word endings are: 'e', 'yje', 'ėje'."
            },
            {
                "type": "multiChoice",
                "question": "Which word is in the Locative case: <br>Aš gyvenu mieste. <br>(I live in a city.)",
                "correctAnswer": "mieste",
                "extraAnswers": [
                    "Aš",
                    "Gyvenu"
                ],
                "shuffleAnswers": true
            },
            {
                "type": "inputText",
                "question": "Finish the sentence: Aš gyvenu _____(in the city)",
                "answers": [
                    "mieste"
                ]
            },
            {
                "type": "multiSelect",
                "question": "Which words are <b>not</b> in the Locative case: <br>Katinas valgo name. <br>(The cat is eating in the house.)",
                "correctAnswers": [
                    "Katinas",
                    "valgo"
                ],
                "extraAnswers": [
                    "name"
                ],
                "shuffleAnswers": false
            },
            {
                "type": "multiChoice",
                "question": "What question does the Locative case answer?",
                "correctAnswer": "kur? - where?",
                "extraAnswers": [
                    "ką? - what?",
                    "kuo? - with what?"
                ],
                "shuffleAnswers": true
            },
            {
                "type": "explanation",
                "question": "Exclamatory - Šauksmininkas",
                "explanation": "The Exclamatory case is used to approach/address someone. <br><br>e.g.<b>Tėti</b>, labas! (<b>Dad</b>, hi!)<br><b>Egle</b>, einam į parduotuvę. (<b>Egle</b>, let's go to a shop.)<br><br> The most common word endings are: 'e', 'ai', 'i'."
            },
            {
                "type": "multiChoice",
                "question": "What is the Exclamatory case used for?",
                "correctAnswer": "to address someone",
                "extraAnswers": [
                    "to express location",
                    "to express instrumentality"
                ],
                "shuffleAnswers": true
            },
            {
                "type": "multiSelect",
                "question": "Which phrases don't have any words with the Exclamatory case in them?",
                "correctAnswers": [
                    "Mama eina",
                    "Aš - Petras"
                ],
                "shuffleAnswers": true,
                "extraAnswers": [
                    "Petrai!",
                    "Mama, aš name"
                ]
            }
        ]
    },
    {
        "lessonName": "More Declension",
        "lessonID": 3,
        "hints": 3,
        "exercises": [
            {
                "type": "explanation",
                "question": "'as' Cases",
                "explanation": "As mentioned before, there are lots of different endings for every case and the ending is determined by the 1st (Nominative) or sometimes the 2nd (Genitive) case.<br>Let's look at words ending with 'as':<br><br>1 (Nom.) - stal<b>as</b><br>2 (Gen.) - stal<b>o</b><br>3 (Dat.) - stal<b>ui</b> <br>4 (Accus.) - stal<b>ą</b><br>5 (Instrum.) - stal<b>u</b><br>6 (Locat.) - stal<b>e</b><br>7 (Excl.) - stal<b>e</b> (For names, the ending is '<b>ai</b>' (Aleks<b>ai</b>)"
            },
            {
                "type": "multiChoice",
                "question": "Which case is 'stalo'?",
                "correctAnswer": "2nd Genitive",
                "extraAnswers": [
                    "1st Nominative",
                    "4th Accusative"
                ],
                "shuffleAnswers": true
            },
            {
                "type": "inputText",
                "question": "Write 'stalas' in the Genitive case.",
                "answers": [
                    "stalo"
                ],
                "shuffleAnswers": true
            },
            {
                "type": "multiChoice",
                "question": "Which case is 'stalą'?",
                "correctAnswer": "4th Accusative",
                "extraAnswers": [
                    "1st Nominative",
                    "2nd Genitive"
                ],
                "shuffleAnswers": true
            },
            {
                "type": "inputText",
                "question": "Write 'Tomas' in the Accusative case.",
                "answers": [
                    "Tomą"
                ],
                "shuffleAnswers": true
            },
            {
                "type": "multiChoice",
                "question": "Which case is 'mano'?",
                "correctAnswer": "2nd Genitive",
                "extraAnswers": [
                    "1st Nominative",
                    "6th Locative"
                ],
                "shuffleAnswers": true
            },
            {
                "type": "multiChoice",
                "question": "Which case is 'stale'?",
                "correctAnswer": "6th Locative",
                "extraAnswers": [
                    "2nd Genitive",
                    "4th Accusative"
                ],
                "shuffleAnswers": true
            },
            {
                "type": "multiChoice",
                "question": "Which word is in the Vocative case for 'Tomas'?",
                "correctAnswer": "Tomai!",
                "extraAnswers": [
                    "Tome!",
                    "Tomo!"
                ],
                "shuffleAnswers": true
            },
            {
                "type": "explanation",
                "question": "'ė' Cases",
                "explanation": "Let's look at words ending with 'ė':<br><br>1 (Nom.) - kėd<b>ė</b><br>2 (Gen.) - kėd<b>ės</b><br>3 (Dat.) - kėd<b>ei</b><br>4 (Accus.) - kėd<b>ę</b><br>5 (Instr.) - kėd<b>e</b><br>6 (Loc.) - kėd<b>ėje</b><br>7 (Excl.) - kėd<b>e</b>"
            },
            {
                "type": "multiChoice",
                "question": "Which case is 'kėdės'?",
                "correctAnswer": "2nd Genitive",
                "extraAnswers": [
                    "1st Nominative",
                    "4th Accusative"
                ],
                "shuffleAnswers": true
            },
            {
                "type": "multiChoice",
                "question": "Which case is 'kėdėje'?",
                "correctAnswer": "6th Locative",
                "extraAnswers": [
                    "2nd Genitive",
                    "4th Accusative"
                ],
                "shuffleAnswers": true
            },
            {
                "type": "inputText",
                "question": "Write 'kėdė' in the Accusative case.",
                "answers": [
                    "kėdę"
                ]
            },
            {
                "type": "multiSelect",
                "question": "Which case is <b>not</b> the Dative case for 'katė'?",
                "correctAnswers": [
                    "katę",
                    "katėje"
                ],
                "shuffleAnswers": true,
                "extraAnswers": [
                    "katei"
                ]
            },
            {
                "type": "explanation",
                "question": "Special Cases of Cases",
                "explanation": "Some prepositions and verbs are always accompanied by a specific case (As if cases weren't hard enough)."
            },
            {
                "type": "explanation",
                "question": "Relative Location and Prepositions",
                "explanation": "If we use common sense, the the phrases 'under a table', 'on the table' should utilise the Locative case, <u>however</u> these phrases invole Prepositions, so they're special.<br><br><b>Po</b> (under) + stalu  - Instrumental<br><b>Ant</b> (on) + stalo - Genitive<br><b>Į</b> (to) + stalą - Accusative (ends with letters 'ą', 'ę', 'į')<br><b>Po</b> kate<br><b>Ant</b> katės<br><b>Į</b> katę - Accusative"
            },
            {
                "type": "multiChoice",
                "question": "What case do you use with the Preposition 'Po' (Under)",
                "correctAnswer": "Instrumentative (5th)",
                "extraAnswers": [
                    "Nominative (1st)",
                    "Exclamatory (7th)"
                ],
                "shuffleAnswers": true
            },
            {
                "type": "multiChoice",
                "question": "What case do you use with the Preposition 'Į' (to)",
                "correctAnswer": "Accusative (4th)",
                "extraAnswers": [
                    "Nominative (1st)",
                    "Genitive (2nd)"
                ],
                "shuffleAnswers": true
            },
            {
                "type": "multiChoice",
                "question": "What case do you use with the Preposition 'Ant' (On)",
                "correctAnswer": "Genitive (2nd)",
                "extraAnswers": [
                    "Nominative (1st)",
                    "Accusative (4th)"
                ],
                "shuffleAnswers": true
            },
            {
                "type": "multiChoice",
                "question": "Which phrase is <b>incorrect</b>",
                "correctAnswer": "Po stale",
                "extraAnswers": [
                    "Po stalu",
                    "Po kėde"
                ],
                "shuffleAnswers": true
            },
            {
                "type": "multiChoice",
                "question": "Which case do you use with the Preposition 'Į'?",
                "correctAnswer": "Accusative (5th)",
                "extraAnswers": [
                    "Locative (6th)",
                    "Genitive (2nd)"
                ],
                "shuffleAnswers": true
            },
            {
                "type": "inputText",
                "question": "Finish the senctence: <br>An orange is under the table <br?'Apelsinas____'",
                "answers": [
                    "yra po stalu",
                    "po stalu"
                ]
            },
            {
                "type": "inputText",
                "question": "Finish the sentence with a Preposition: <br>I am going to the shop. <br>'Aš einu __ parduotuvę.",
                "answers": [
                    "į"
                ]
            },
            {
                "type": "explanation",
                "question": "Special Verbs and Cases",
                "explanation": "Some special verbs are also only used with specific cases.<br><br>Aš noriu (I want + Genitive (2nd)<br>Man reikia (I need) + Genitive<br>You could add the words 'for myself' to both verbs, the 2nd case satisfies the Possession property<br><br>Aš noriu <b>katino</b> (I want a cat)<br>Man reikia <b>kėdės</b> (I need a chair)"
            },
            {
                "type": "multiChoice",
                "question": "Which case do you use 'noriu' with?",
                "correctAnswer": "Genitive (2nd)",
                "extraAnswers": [
                    "Nominative (1st)",
                    "Instrumental (5th)"
                ],
                "shuffleAnswers": true
            },
            {
                "type": "inputText",
                "question": "Write: 'I need a house'",
                "answers": [
                    "Man reikia namo."
                ]
            },
            {
                "type": "inputText",
                "question": "Write: 'chair' in the Accusative (4th) case",
                "answers": [
                    "kėdę"
                ]
            },
            {
                "type": "inputText",
                "question": "Write: 'chair' in the Nominative (1st) case",
                "answers": [
                    "kėdė"
                ]
            },
            {
                "type": "multiChoice",
                "question": "Consider the sentence: <br>An orange is under the table.<br> Which case would you use to describe 'table' ",
                "correctAnswer": "Instrumentative (5th) - stalu",
                "extraAnswers": [
                    "Accusative (4th) - stalą",
                    "Genitive (2nd) - stalo"
                ],
                "shuffleAnswers": true
            },
            {
                "type": "multiChoice",
                "question": "Consider the sentence: <br>Simona wants an orange<br> Which case would you use to describe 'orange' ",
                "correctAnswer": "Genitive (2nd) - apelsino",
                "extraAnswers": [
                    "Accusative (4th) - apelsiną",
                    "Nominative (1st) - apelsinas"
                ],
                "shuffleAnswers": true
            },
            {
                "type": "inputText",
                "question": "Write: 'In the cat (male)'",
                "answers": [
                    "katine"
                ]
            },
            {
                "type": "inputText",
                "question": "Write: 'In the cat (female)'",
                "answers": [
                    "katėje"
                ]
            },
            {
                "type": "multiSelect",
                "question": "In which phrase would you use the Genitive case (2nd)?",
                "correctAnswers": [
                    "Aš noriu ___",
                    "Ant ____"
                ],
                "shuffleAnswers": true,
                "extraAnswers": [
                    "Po ____"
                ]
            },
            {
                "type": "multiChoice",
                "question": "Which word is in the Nominative (1st) case?",
                "correctAnswer": "Namas",
                "extraAnswers": [
                    "Labas",
                    "Kėdės"
                ],
                "shuffleAnswers": true
            },
            {
                "type": "multiChoice",
                "question": "Finish the sentence: 'Bulvė yra ___ stalu' (The potato is under a table)",
                "correctAnswer": "po",
                "extraAnswers": [
                    "už",
                    "ant"
                ],
                "shuffleAnswers": true
            },
            {
                "type": "multiSelect",
                "question": "Select all cases that don't exist in the Lithuanian language.",
                "correctAnswers": [
                    "Monative",
                    "Incurative"
                ],
                "shuffleAnswers": true,
                "extraAnswers": [
                    "Dative",
                    "Instrumentative"
                ]
            },
            {
                "type": "multiSelect",
                "question": "Select all propositions:",
                "correctAnswers": [
                    "po",
                    "ant",
                    "į"
                ],
                "shuffleAnswers": true,
                "extraAnswers": [
                    "ą",
                    "Mes"
                ]
            },
            {
                "type": "multiChoice",
                "question": "What Preposition would you use with the Instrumentative case?",
                "correctAnswer": "po",
                "extraAnswers": [
                    "ant",
                    "už"
                ],
                "shuffleAnswers": true
            }
        ]
    }
]